<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrollText</string>
    <string name="article_title">Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="article_subheading">About Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="article_text">The domains <i>wikipedia.com</i> and <i>wikipedia.org</i> were registered on January 12, 2001, and January 13, 2001, respectively,
        and Wikipedia was launched on January 15, 2001, as a single English-language edition at www.wikipedia.com, and announced by Sanger on the Nupedia mailing list.
        Wikipedia\'s policy of \"neutral point-of-view\" was codified in its first few months.
        Otherwise, there were relatively few rules initially and Wikipedia operated independently of Nupedia. Originally, Bomis intended to make Wikipedia a business for profit.
        \n\n
        In November 2009, a researcher at the Rey Juan Carlos University in Madrid found that the English Wikipedia had lost 49,000 editors during the
        first three months of 2009; in comparison, the project lost only 4,900 editors during the same period in 2008. <i>The Wall Street Journal</i> cited
        the array of rules applied to editing and disputes related to such content among the reasons for this trend. Wales disputed these claims in 2009,
        denying the decline and questioning the methodology of the study. Two years later, in 2011, Wales acknowledged the presence of a slight decline, noting a
        decrease from \"a little more than 36,000 writers\" in June 2010 to 35,800 in June 2011. In the same interview, Wales also claimed the number of editors was
        \"stable and sustainable\". A 2013 article titled \"The Decline of Wikipedia\" in <i>MIT Technology Review</i> questioned this claim. The article revealed that since 2007,
        Wikipedia had lost a third of its volunteer editors, and those still there have focused increasingly on minutiae. In July 2012, <i>The Atlantic</i> reported that the number
        of administrators is also in decline. In the November 25, 2013,
        issue of <i>New York</i> magazine, Katherine Ward stated \"Wikipedia, the sixth-most-used website, is facing an internal crisis\".
    </string>
</resources>